[
  {
    "question": "What was Harry Potter's full name?",
    "options": [
      "Harry James Potter",
      "Harry William Potter",
      "Harry John Potter",
      "Harry Lee Potter"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Harry James Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical school does Harry Potter attend?",
    "options": [
      "Ilvermorny",
      "Beauxbatons Academy of Magic",
      "Durmstrang Institute",
      "Hogwarts"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the headmaster of Hogwarts?",
    "options": [
      "Minerva McGonagall",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Albus Dumbledore",
      "Rubeus Hagrid"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Albus Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the dark force that feeds on happiness and souls?",
    "options": ["Dementors", "Boggarts", "Acromantulas", "Inferi"],
    "correctAnswer": "Dementors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subject did Severus Snape teach at Hogwarts?",
    "options": ["Transfiguration", "Potions", "Herbology", "Divination"],
    "correctAnswer": "Potions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the house-elf who helped Harry Potter?",
    "options": ["Winky", "Kreacher", "Dobby", "Hokey"],
    "correctAnswer": "Dobby"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell did Harry Potter use to summon his broomstick?",
    "options": ["Expelliarmus", "Alohomora", "Accio", "Expecto Patronum"],
    "correctAnswer": "Accio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the names of the three main characters - Harry, Ron, and...?",
    "options": ["Hermione", "Luna", "Neville", "Draco"],
    "correctAnswer": "Hermione"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the main villain in the Harry Potter series?",
    "options": [
      "Lucius Malfoy",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Bellatrix Lestrange",
      "Voldemort"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal appears to Harry Potter from the Patronus spell?",
    "options": ["Dragon", "Unicorn", "Phoenix", "Stag"],
    "correctAnswer": "Stag"
  }
]
